<resources>
    <string name="app_name">NITRR</string>
    <string name="intro">Located in the capital city of Chhattisgarh, National Institute of Technology Raipur or NIT Raipur (NITRR) was formerly known as Government Engineering College. It was established in 1956 by Rajendra Prasad, the first President of India. Ranked 67 for Engineering by NIRF in 2020, it is recognised as the Institute of National Importance and funded by the Government of India under the National Institutes of Technology Act, 2007. NIT Raipur offers BTech, BArch, MCA, MTech and PhD courses across 19 departments of study.</string>
    <string name="highlight">NIT Raipur Highlights 2021</string>
    <string name="tabletitle">The following table shows NIT Raipur highlights 2021:</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="admpro1">One needs to take the JEE (Main) exam and pass the Class XII board examination. Read JEE Main Performance Criteria in Class XII.</string>
    <string name="admpro2">Admissions are done on the basis of rank in JEE (Main) through JoSAA Counselling and CSAB Special Round.</string>
    <string name="centrallib">The Central Library of NIT, Raipur has a good collection of more than 1 lakh of print books , more than 1.7 lacs e-books consisting of both text and reference books Ph.D theses, online journal Archive collections and online protocols . Besides it subscribes to a good number of full text online databases ,Indian print journals . The Central Library is fully automated through LibSys7- Library management software .The Web OPAC is fully functional. RFID system has been installed in the Reading Room of Central Library.It also has Discovery Service ,Remote access facilities and plagiarism check software like Turnitin Feedback Studio and URKUND .It caters to the information and document need of nearly 5000 users consisting of Faculty members, staff, B.Tech/M.Tech/MCA students and research scholars satisfactorily.</string>
    <string name="hostel">The institute provides a limited residential facility for boys and girls students. There are 05 boys and 03 girls’ hostels within the campus. For further details about hostels,please visit the following links.</string>
    <string name="medical">The Nit Dispensary Raipur is situated by the side of NCC office having three rooms two rooms for the Doctors and one room is for the staff of the Dispensary. Emergency Contract Number :- 09589489844 - for AMBULANCE 09009331080- for NIT DISPENSARY (JAY PRAKASH NAYAK)</string>
    <string name="medicalavailable"><![CDATA[Medical Facility Available :- Free OPD Consultation to all the staff & students of NIT Raipur Free Distribution of Medicines to all the staffs & students of NIT Raipur Free Ambulance Service for hospitalization to staff & students of NIT Raipur All the Regular employees of NIT Raipur Gets their MR Claim as per CGHS Rates]]></string>
    <string name="guesthouse">Guest House of the institute provides accommodation facility to the institute guests, guests of the faculty/staff members of the institute, parents of the students, visitors from other NITs and educational institutes, participants of the activities organised by the institute and persons with approval from appropriate authorities. Guest house has three living rooms, one dining hall and one hall. All rooms are equipped with state of art facilities like AC, TV, and Refrigerator etc.</string>
    <string name="estateoffice"><![CDATA[The Estate maintenance department (Civil & Electrical) maintains Civil & Electrical services for the entire campus which includes Institute buildings, Hostels, Residential quarters and other premises. The department provides water supply services to complete campus through institutes own supply system & Electrical supply through 33 KV High tension line with 33 KV/0.4 KV Transformers through institutes own UG Electrical Distribution Network & separate street lighting system arrangement is available with internal length of around 5 K.M. controlled through timer control system. The department also provides Electrical back up to the prominent places ie Server system, computer centers, administrative offices etc. the routine complaints also attended by department through available staff for maintenance services. Apart from this Estate Civil & Electrical department also carry out new work/ renovation activities for existing premises as well as for new proposed premises within the institute jurisdiction.]]></string>
    <string name="sports">The Institute provides ample avenues for the development and nurturing of creative and other talents in the students through Sports Department. All the activities are managed by students under the guidance of SAS Officer and Faculty In-Charge Sports. The prime bodies under sports department is activity center and GYM, which provide avenues for various sports events, indoor and outdoor games. Students are also encouraged and facilitated to take part in similar events in other institutions. Sports Department National Institute of Technology Raipur has been known for its excellence, in Sports and the students keep raising the bar for themselves by proving to be a step ahead of the crowd, time and again. The institute, at the same time, also has records of achievements in curricular as well as extra-curricular activities. An extremely crucial role is played by Sports department of the institute in facilitating the activities and reaching out to the students. GYM is an Institute governed organization that cultivates leadership, encourages students to participate in outdoor activities, and provide facilities for games and sports. The members of the staff monitor activities of Gym and help students in organizing and managing their functions. Sports department provides facilities for outdoor games like Athletics, Cricket, Football, Hockey, Badminton, Basketball, Baseball, Lawn Tennis, Swimming, Gymnastics, Yoga Exercises, and Volleyball etc. Each game is looked after by a Captain and Sports Officer. All the games are properly run with the assistance of Sports Officer.</string>
    <string name="store1"><![CDATA[The Institute has received a proposal from National Rural Livelihood Mission (NRLM), Zila Panchayat, Raipur, expressing interest for opening an All-in-One Store and a Photocopy and printing service shop under livelihood mission ‘BIHAN’ with in the premises of NITRR. The NRLM of state of Chhattisgarh attaches economically backward rural women to community organizations and works towards empowering these women by imparting them training to ensure livelihood earning and consolidates their social and economic status. In this way NRLM also works towards serving the nation by empowering Women as defined under the objectives of various schemes offered by Ministry of Women & Child Development, GOI. With this proposal of NRLM, the Institute also has a prospect of honoring its social accountabilities for the society and region by enabling the economic development of the community of economically backward Women attached to NRLM, Zila Panchayat (Raipur) CG, thus leading to Empowerment of Women. As the said facilities are presently not available and the institute provides hostel and residence to approximately 2000 students and nearly 100 staff and faculty families whose needs could be catered by the All-In-One store. Such facilities will be of use to the day scholars and visitors too during the regular working hours of the Institute.]]></string>
    <string name="strore2">Stores</string>
    <string name="store3">The Juice corner is now functioning at the campus of NIT Raipur since January 08, 2019. The operating time of Juice Corner is 8.00 AM to 8.00 PM daily. The facility of fresh Fruits Juice Corner is very useful for the students, guests, faculty and staff. The Coffee Day Beverages (Coffee day Global Ltd) is now functioning at the campus of NIT Raipur since February 22, 2019. The operating time of Juice Corner is 8.00 AM to 10.00 PM daily. The facility of different types of hot and cold beverages is very useful for the students, guests, faculty and staff.</string>
    <string name="revvv">Our college is good, but it needs to improve a little in terms of providing exposure. Placements: Campus placements are not available for architecture students so that you won\'t get jobs after passed out of college. But here we are taught to be our own boss and not to work under any boss. We are also taught to start our own business and practice. Infrastructure: All the facilities like Wi-Fi facility, labs, studios, library, toilets, girls common room, computer lab, etc., are available. Only washrooms are a little disorganised. The infrastructure of our college is the same as the infrastructure of a government college, but the degree matters a lot. NIT Raipur comes under top 25 colleges in India. Faculty: It\'s a tough course, and interest must be needed, and you should give priority towards dedication for the course. Many fun events and cultural events are conducted here. If you start enjoying the course, then it will provide you great success. Other: The best thing about the course is that it provides chances to roam around the cities and countries for study purpose. It enables students to develop themselves overall, not just to gain marks but also the personality.</string>
</resources>